This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger and King of the Pirates.
Bunkini Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Stop this sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
With only four hours left until the public execution of his brother Ace,
Luffy rushes to the top floor of Impel Down.
Unfortunately, before he can escape the prison,
he is once again attacked by Warden Magellan who unleashes his poisonous power.
What the hell?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
There's not a single lady ship in sight!
No, they're close.
Look, and you can see the shadows of their sails on the fog.
There they are, an entire fleet of ships.
I'm going to launch you guys on the deck, so hold on tight now.
Huh? Wait, you're what?
You maybe want to run that plan past us one more time, fish face?
What the?
That bastard's gone!
What the hell's going on?
Ocean Courant!
Overthrow!
They're going to try to hijack the ship!
Stop them!
Attack them with everything you've got!
They've got devil fruit powers!
Just throw them in the water!
The escapee team in trouble!
The forbidden move!
Venom Demon!
Anyone else?
Ivan!
Robin!
A nitrogen!
A carbon!
so you're gonna toss us in the water or what i think you need to learn your own limitations
stand firm throw them overboard
what's that
it's jean fei behold my fish man karate
watch your aim
oh we were going to use that ship weren't we once i enter the water i'm afraid my strength runs wild
kum kum
Champion!
How's that?
All right! One more port!
Ready? And fire!
There's no use trying to stall for time.
I've ordered all Navy vessels to distance themselves from the prison.
Even if you made it outside,
there's no ship for you to escape on.
What do you know? That fish man guy's got it under control!
Whatever it takes, they'll find a way out of this!
Jinbei is a worthy adversary in the water.
All the more reason for me to finish you quickly.
To theabet favorite Pokemon
If you haven'tgarty or you'll beileri
Don't do it, Strawhead!
This is over the limit! Run for your life!
Champion!
Oh, yeah!
God!
Don't do it, Strawberry.
Don't do it, Straw Hat! This is over the limit!
Run for your life!
Champion!
It had a good run, but my wax can't help you anymore!
Wax! Wax!
Scary!
Alright.
Ah, wait.
We have got ammo.
Now perish.
Venom demon!
Ah!
We better run!
Yeah, you think!
Ah!
Hell's judgment!
Die!
He got me!
Please don't leave me!
Help!
No, dammit, don't touch me!
Why, when I was so close?
Ah!
It looks like it's not just my wax!
That poison is spreading over everything it touches!
Like a tidal wave of very bad news!
Oh, it's cool, well-lasted!
But yeah, that does look pretty bad!
Hurry up, straw boy! You gotta make it!
What about the ships?
I can hear gunfire, but the fog's too heavy to make out anything!
This is driving me crazy, man!
I know they're plenty capable of stealing a ship,
but if the marines delay them long enough, we're screwed!
Sounds like they're pretty far out!
Even if they do nab a ship, they'll have to drag it all the way back here for us to get on it!
No way! Magellan's probably gonna catch up to us any minute now!
I know Straw Hat survived a fight with him once, but nobody can stop Magellan and this is taking awfully long!
Straw boy?
Dede, hurry!
We're counting on you!
No!
Throw them all!
Don't let them take the ship!
Damn you!
Did his arm just turn into a knife?
What's up with this guy?
It's the Diced Ice Fruit.
I remember that bastard!
He's an assassin from the West Blue!
Das Bones!
D´D Diniz
Gופ!!
Grrrrghhh!
It's a matter of time before they take this ship.
I refuse to suffer that dishonor.
Have the cannon sink it!
Sir!
Ready, cannon!
Huh? Oh, no, not again!
Oh, the gunpowder! It's soaked!
Jinbei, huh?
Keep him locked down! Open fire!
He's right behind us! We've got to run faster!
Jinbei!
Basket Buggy!
Jin! You there, we're coming!
Huh? I hear straw boy!
Run for it!
I don't know what that thing is, but holy crap!
It's Magellan!
No! We're all gonna die!
Did you get a ship?
Not yet! We can't tell what the heck's going on up there!
What?!
The hormones I injected got me this far.
But I think I'm spent.
I can't take a single step more.
Oh, a wink!
No!
Huh?
Oh!
Is that Eva?
Don't scare us like that!
Oh, I made it!
Yay, it's nappy time!
No, not nappy time! You have a head injury!
Thank goodness! You're alive! I was so scared! I can't lose you!
Still breathing, are you?
Hey, Straw Hat! Call from Jinbei!
A baby transponder snail?
Excellent work, gentlemen!
Now you show up.
Kalik!
Luffy!
You reached the exit?
Uh-huh!
But Magellan's still after us!
We're kinda running out of places to run!
I see!
It took a while, but we do have a ship!
We'll be there soon, but I need you to trust me!
Just keep running!
Jump straight into the water!
Huh?
That goes for you and all of the prisoners!
Are you out of your mind?!
You realize this is a clone belt, right?!
Sorry, but I don't have time to explain right now!
Let's do it!
Three, I need another wax thingy!
We're dead!
Either we drown or Magellan destroys us!
Why do you trust that fish man anyway?
He's a warlord!
He's probably trying to curry favor with the government!
Ace's friends are my friends too!
He won't let us down!
Into the water?
Go ahead!
Let the Sea Kings eat you and save me the trouble of cleaning up the mess!
Be careful!
Even a drop of that poison would kill you!
Bye, Magellan!
To the end of the ship!
Hell's judgment once more!
Forget!
This is as big as I can make it!
One candle wall coming right up!
I've had enough of your nonsense!
You better make it quick, Straw Hat!
I'm losing it any second now!
Queime, guaaaaaaaaaaat!
SHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGGES!
Death!!!
Whoa!
And he rushed him back!
Let's get back!
The poison is still seeping through!
Do we gotta dive into the water after all?
We're dead!
Hey, Eva, wake up! Hurry!
Big trouble! I need your fat head to do something!
I'm all tiny right now, and you're the strongest person here!
Uh, what's that?
We gotta get out of here!
Who are you? Baby straw boy?
Do the wing thing! Do it!
Okey doke!
No, please! What? Help!
Here we go!
Wayne, you're not on your right mind!
There's no way that's their plan!
They won't survive two minutes in those waters without a ship,
and they know it!
Everybody grab onto Eva's face!
Do what now?
Whatever you're trying to do, stop it!
Sure, whatever!
I'll try anything!
No, I changed my mind!
I want the satisfaction of killing you myself!
Hold on!
Help me!
I said stop!
They're falling!
Something huge is under the ship!
A swarm of sea kings!
You gotta keep flying!
He can't hear you!
I think he passed out!
We landed on something!
Look down!
I can't believe this!
How are we still alive?
I'm glad you made it!
You must forgive me for making such an outlandish request back there!
It's a school of whale sharks!
Ji-Fei must have called them!
Awesome!
Woofie and company have finally escaped from Impel Down!
But there's no time for celebration, with the Gate of Justice closed in front of them
and a swarm of Navy pursuers behind them!
Then, just when all hope seems lost, one of their comrades makes an all-or-nothing gamble
that could turn everything around!
On the next One Piece!
Come, Final Miracle!
Break through the Gate of Justice!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!